嘿  亲爱的  我突然有个念头
Hey, you know what I was thinking, honey?
我认为这个周末我们应该
We should have a little romantic getaway.
来个浪漫的二人世界
This weekend just you and me.
父母大人  不要说了  我们正在吃饭呢
Guys, please, we're trying to eat here.
我觉着这想法不错  我们去哪
I think that sounds fun. Where should we go?
怀俄明州的卡斯柏
Casper, Wyoming...
注：怀俄明州人口稀少  地理位置偏僻
是怀俄明州
The most romantic city.
最浪漫的城市
In Wyoming.
难道今年的灭虫大会是在卡斯柏召开吗
Is the bug convention in Casper this year?
什么灭虫大会
The bug convention?
别急  我查下日历
Well, I'll just check the old calendar.
哈  真被你说中了
Ha! Now that is a coincidence.
嘿  老妈  我觉着你应该去
Hey, mom, I think you should go.
为什么  难道你想趁我们不在家开派对吗
Why? You planning to throw a party while we're gone?
又被你说中了
Now that is a coincidence.
噢  别作梦了  派对夭折了  我哪也不去
Oh. Well, party's off. I'm not going.
为什么不去啊  老妈
Why not, mom?
灭虫大会听起来挺
Bug convention sounds like a lot of...
我都说不下去了
I can't even get through it.
在灭虫大会上你们都做些什么啊
What do you even do at a bug convention?
无事可做  就是一大堆灭虫专家
Nothing. It's just a bunch of exterminators.
在一个狭小的会议室里讨论灭虫剂
In a cramped conference room talking about deadly gas.
无聊就此来临
And then it gets boring.
亲爱的  首先  我们不是一堆  是一群
First of all, honey, we are not a bunch. We are a swarm.
明白吗
<i>Huh?!</i>
我们说一堆好玩的虫子专业术语
We got a lot of fun bug-related lingo like that,
比如  我们不住屋子  我们筑巢
Like we don't get rooms, we nest.
我们不吃饭  我们进食
We don't dine, we feed.
不敢相信我会说出这句话  有人能送我去学校吗
I can't believe I'm saying this, but can someone drive me to school?
好了  孩子们  你们听好了
All right, guys, you know what?
防治害虫就是我谋生的手段
Pest control is what I do for a living.
我知道对你们说他们只是老鼠  蟑螂  蛆虫
I know it just may be rats and roaches and maggots to you,
但是对于我来说  他们就是面包和黄油
But it's my bread and butter.
那我以后拒绝进食面包和黄油了
And I'm done with my bread and butter.
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z  万山绿遍
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第二十一集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E21  Termite Queen
-老妈  好  -嘿  儿子
-Hey, mom. -Hey, honey.
还记着我去KCU大学的事吗
Remember when I went off to college to K.C.U.?
咕唧炸鸡大学  培养人才的摇篮
Kwikki chikki university, the we can trainning someone are
记忆犹新
I remember it well.
那个  回首那些疯狂的大学岁月
Well, back in those crazy college days...
应该是两天的大学岁月
Those two crazy college days.
我认识了一个叫肉汁的家伙
I met this guy named Gravy
我告诉他如果搬进城里来
And I told him , he could moved in town,
可以和咱们住在一起
He could stay with us.
而我也刚刚发现他已经到丹佛了
And I just found out he's moving to Denver,
而且他准备要在咕唧炸鸡工作了
And he's gonna be working at kwikki chikki.
好了  我大概明白了  他什么时候来
Okay, I think I see what is this going, when is this happening?
派对
<i>Party!</i>
就是现在
Right about now.
PJ  我不敢相信你居然
P.J., I can't believe you
-肉汁兄  -PJ
-Gravy! -P.J.!
这是咕唧炸鸡的握手方式
That was the kwikki chikki handshake.
百闻不如一见
I was hoping.
老兄  你没说过你有个这么漂亮的姐姐
Dude, you didn't tell me your sister was so hot.
肉汁  想住多久都可以
Gravy, stay as long as you like.
这里太爽了
Sweet crib!
老兄  真高兴你能来这里
Dude, I'm so psyched you're here, dude.
-绝对爽爆了  -史诗般的
-This is gonna be a blast. -Epic!
-再想想在大学时候的狂野岁月  -没错
-Just think of all those wild times at college. -Yeah.
老兄  还记着汉堡包技校美女
Dude, remember the time the girls from hamburger tech
和咱们开派对的日子吗
came and partied with us?
记着  记着
Yeah yeah!
你还记着那次
Or what about the time...
好像就有那一件事可说
I think that's the only story we have.
嘿  老妈  听听这个
Hey, mom, listen to this.
“知心大姐”的意见栏
It's from that advice column "dear Tammy."
上面说“知心大姐  您好
It says, "dear Tammy,
最近我有一辆只开了二十分钟的车
Recently a car I owned for 20 minutes.
不幸报废了
Was sadly wrecked.
“我应该怎么对父母说  我想再要一辆”
"How do I ask my parents for another one?"
-怎么和你的经历这么像  -没错
-That's almost exactly what happened to you. -I know.
接着知心大姐回复了
So then dear Tammy replied,
“如果你的父母爱你  那他们会给你买一辆新车的
"if your parents love you, they will buy you a new car.
他们不会后悔的”
And be glad they did."
-好诡异啊  -是啊
-That is so strange. -Yeah.
因为知心大姐三年前就去世了
Because dear Tammy passed away three years ago.
是吗  这位已逝大姐的愿景多么好啊
Well, that's a pretty good answer for a dead lady, right?
老妈  拜托了
Mom, please,
那二十分钟的驾驶体验让我无法释怀
owning that car was the best 20 minutes of my life.
宝贝  如果就我一个人说了算  我会给你买的
Honey, if it were up to me, I'd buy you a new car.
问题在于你爸
The problem is your father.
他最近正在攒钱
He's been on a tear lately about saving money.
他太不正常了
What is wrong with him?
总是在攒钱  计划将来
He's always saving and planning for the future.
爷爷奶奶对他做了些什么
What did grandma and grandpa do to him?
你到底多渴望这辆新车
How badly do you want this car?
-都渴死了  -请坐下
-Really badly. -Sit down.
泰迪
Teddy,
你爸是个头脑简单的人
Your father is a simple man.
-是的  赞同你的说法  -好的
-Yes, I'm with you so far. -Okay.
如果你想从他手里得到点东西
If you want something from him,
那你就要想法设法讨好他
Then you need to do something he wants to do.
正当他逍遥快活之时  你要像眼镜蛇一样出击
Then when he's in his happy place, just strike like a cobra.
好了  你在说什么呢
Okay, what are you talking about?
灭虫大会啊  泰迪
The bug convention, Teddy...
灭虫大会
The bug convention.
你和他一起去  他就会高兴
You go there with your father and he will be so happy...
他一高兴  就给你买车了
He will buy you a car.
妙计  那我就前往灭虫大会  能有多惨
Perfect. I'll go to the bug convention. How bad could it be?
超乎你的想象
You have no idea.
我曾去过一次
I went to one convention.
到现在我仍在做噩梦
I still have the dreams.
嘿  盖比  你猜我得到了什么
Hey, Gabe, guess what I got.
上一次  是虱子
Last time we played this game, it was lice.
我妈给了我这个超炫摄像机
My mom gave me this cool new video camera.
因为我被棒球队开除了
For getting cut from the baseball team.
被开除怎么会得到一部摄像机呢
How does getting cut from the team get you a camera?
她替我感到难过
She felt bad for me,
而且我爸因为我去面试棒球队  而送给我一个滑板
and my dad gave me a skateboard for trying out.
我爱死运动了
I love sports.
真不赖
This is pretty cool.
-我们应该拍部电影  -好主意
-We should make a movie. -Yeah.
你看起来不上镜
The camera does not love you.
我还是挺上镜的  所以我是主演
But it does love me. So I should be the star.
哥们  你越来越像你老妈了
Dude, you're getting more like your mom every day.
我们应该拍什么类型的电影
So what kind of movie should we make?
爱情喜剧怎么样
How about a romantic comedy?
大家都喜欢爱喜
Everyone loves a good romcom.
你说话的时候  我突然想到了
I thought of something while you were talking.
不如拍个怪兽电影
Let's make a monster movie.
酷  但是我们去哪找个可怕的怪兽
Cool, but where are we gonna find a scary monster?
吥
Boo!
看来怪兽是找到了
I think we found our monster.
好了  好了
Done, done...
还没好
And not done.
你好啊  艾·邓肯
How are you doing, A. Dunc?
艾·邓肯
A. Dunc?
噢  是的  我给你起了个新名字
Oh, yeah. That's my new name for you.
我觉着艾米这名字不好听
Amy just wasn't kind of working for me.
他多讨人爱啊
Aren't you loving him?
爱  算了
Loving? No no.
喜欢  也算了
Liking? No.
是谁让我火冒三丈
Getting on my very last nerve?
叮  叮  叮  我知道是谁了
Ding ding ding! We have a winner.
亲爱的肉汁  你是不是把什么东西落在厨房了
Gravy honey, did you forget something in the kitchen?
没有  我没落
No, I'm good.
我是指你的裤子
I meant your pants.
我知道  我只是喜欢回家后就脱掉
Yeah, I know. I just like to take those off when I get home.
让我有一种解脱的感觉
It's kind of how I unwind.
好了  好了  我知道你希望舒服自在
Okay, look, I get it that you're trying to be comfortable.
但这在邓肯家是不允许的
That is not how we roll in the Duncan house.
老兄  你说的没错  这太舒服了
Dude, you're right. This is so much more comfortable.
亲爱的  你不会相信的
Honey, you're not gonna believe this.
泰迪想和我一起去灭虫大会
Teddy wants to go to the bug convention with me.
难道现在是脱裤时间吗
Are we going pantsless now?
今天真是太爽了
This is the best day ever!
《巨婴来袭》
"attack of the 50-foot baby, "
第一幕  第一场
Scene 1, take 1.
好了  你扮演的是疯狂科学家  开拍
Okay, you're a mad scientist. Action!
如今我研究出了终极生长配方
Now that I've finished my super growth formula,
我们用一颗普通的葡萄来进行试验
It's time to test it out on an ordinary grape.
停
Cut.
开拍
Action.
成功了  在水果上成功了
It works on fruit, It works on fruit,
但是如果在人类上进行实验呢
But what about on human beings?
我会甘当试验品
I'll test it out myself.
但是我要先看看我的宝贝
But first let me check on my baby.
宝贝  噢  宝贝
Baby. Oh, baby!
查莉  过来  过来
Charlie, come here. Come here.
-你能喝点东西吗  -不
-Can you go drink the stuff now? -No.
是果汁
It's just juice.
停
And cut.
哥们  你小妹搞什么鬼  她一定要喝下去
Dude, what's your sister's problem? She's gotta drink the stuff.
她才两岁
She's two.
我两岁的时候  什么都喝
When I was two, I drank everything.
让我和她谈谈
Just let me talk to her.
宝贝  查莉
Charlie sweetheart,
你做的很好
You're doing great.
拍出的画面无可挑剔  事情是这样的
The picture's gonna look terrific. Here's the thing.
当我们让你喝下去的时候
When we say drink the stuff,
你就要喝下去  明白吗
You gotta drink the stuff, okay?
好了  好了  我们走
Okay, great. Here we go.
你准备好了吗  杰克  你在干什么
Are you ready to... Jake, what are you doing?
那是电影的道具
We need that for the movie.
我在做实验
I'm doing an experiment.
我想看看小便会不会变成蓝色
I wanna see if it turns my pee blue.
PJ
P.J.!
嘿  老妈  什么事
Hey, mom, what's up?
什么事
What's up?
看看你的肉汁在家里干的好事
Look at what Gravy has done to this place.
嘿  他整理干净了
Hey, he tidied up.
我受够了
I've had it.
他又懒  又恶心
He's disgusting. He's a slob.
我忍不了了  我要赶他走
I can't take it anymore. I want him out.
难道这都是厕所里洋葱圈惹的祸
Is this about the onion ring in the toilet?
因为他需要一个靶子
'cause he needs a target.
如果你明天不赶他走
Either you tell him by the end of the day tomorrow,
否则我来
Or I do it.
他可是我大学里最好的哥们儿
But he's my best friend from college.
炸鸡大学  一所就上了2天的炸鸡肉大学有木有
Chicken college, a two-day chicken college!
好吧  行
All right, okay.
不过这事一定要妥善处理
But this has to be done the right way
因为肉汁其实挺敏感的
'cause gravy's actually really sensitive.
唉  坏消息啊  兄弟
All right, bad news, guys.
我刚才喝了一加仑水  还把洋葱卷吃得一干二净
I just drank a gallon of water and we are out of onion rings.
卡斯珀  怀俄明州
Casper, Wyoming,
灭虫大会  穿着工作服的人们
Bug convention, guys in overalls.
该你说了
You talk now.
嗨  开胃小吃  自己拿  甜心
Hey, hors d'oeuvres. Help yourself, honey.
好的
Okay.
不错啊  挺脆的
This is good. It's crunchy.
是冷冻再干燥的蚂蚁
Freeze-dried ants.
这块儿的食物都是用虫子做的  有意思吧
All the food here is insect-based. Isn't that fun?
-鲍伯  -莫雷
-Bob. -Murray.
嘿  这是我的女儿泰迪  欢迎认识
Hey, I would like to introduce you to my daughter Teddy.
嗨  嘿  爸  我的牙缝里还有蚂蚁腿吗
Hi. Hey, dad, do I have any legs in my teeth?
她蛮可爱的
She's a charmer.
嗯  鲍伯  你是来给我的演讲捧场的吗
So, Bob, you gonna pop by my speech?
也可以称为专题演讲  怎么说都行
Keynote address, whatever.
没错  我发明了一种杀灭白蚁的新方法
Yeah, I got a new way to kill termites...
莫雷大法
The Murray method.
好的  其实呢  莫雷  我的演讲就在你后面
Well, actually, Murray, I'm going on right after you.
没错  我发明了一种杀灭白蚁的新方法
Yeah, I got my own new method of killing termites...
大灌篮式
The slam dunc.
不明白
I don't get it.
鲍伯邓肯
Bob Duncan.
邓肯（音同灌篮） 大灌篮
Dunc. Slam dunc.
噢  我懂了因为  不懂
Ooh, I see because... no.
没关系  我相信开完了介绍会你就会一清二楚
Well, I'm sure it will be very clear after the presentation.
我已经看过你的介绍会了  邓肯
I've seen your presentations, Duncan.
缺少活力  没有视觉道具  这就是你的问题
They lack pizzazz. No visual aids. That's your problem.
不要
Pass.
诶  我讨厌这个莫雷
Man, I hate that Murray.
不过你知道吗  有些东西是他所不知道的
But do you know what? Here's what he doesn't know.
今年我会加上一个让全场笑翻天的视觉道具
This year I have a visual aid that is going to blow the roof off this place.
多亏你来了  甜心
thanks to you, honey.
其实我应该叫你
Or should I say.
白蚁女王
Termite queen?
-什么  -没错
-What? -Yeah!
今年你要跟我一起上台
You're gonna be onstage with me this year.
演那个恶心的
Playing the disgustingly
白蚁殖民王国的最高统治者
huge supreme monarch of the termite colony.
但是  但是
But... but...
好吧
Okay.
嘿  肉汁
Hey, gravy.
我能跟你谈一下吗  有件很重要的事
Can I talk to you for a sec? It's kind of important.
没问题  你可以告诉我任何事
Of course. You can tell me anything.
你可是我在咕唧炸鸡最要好的兄弟
You were my best buddy at kwikki chikki.
我能为你赴汤蹈火
I would do anything for you.
也能为你吃鸡腿
I would even eat our chicken for you.
我永远不会让你帮我这个忙
I would never ask you to do that.
好吧
Yeah.
不过问题是  你来我家真是棒极了
But the thing is it's been super great having you here.
是的  是的
Yeah. Yeah.
但是  呃
But... yeah.
唉  开不了口啊
Wow, this is hard.
其实呢  我有件事想跟你说一下
Actually, there was something I wanted to tell you.
艾（米）邓肯  老收拾我的屋子
A. Dunc keeps rearranging my room.
真不厚道  是吧  帮我跟她讲讲
Not cool, all right? Talk to her for me?
兄弟  我都到家一个小时了
Dude, I've been home for like an hour.
还裹着我的大裤衩干啥
What am I still doing with my pants on?
莫雷大法
The Murray method,
一种安全的无毒的杀灭白蚁的万能药
A safe non-toxic elixir for killing termites,
原料来自于普通的橘子
Derived from the common orange.
用了莫雷法  你就会说
Try the Murray method and you'll say,
橘子  你要庆幸你不是只白蚁啊
"Orange you glad you're not a termite?"
上来盖过我吧  邓肯
Try and top that, Duncan.
你赶快夹着尾巴逃走吧
Go squeeze yourself.
嘿  大家好
Hey, everybody,
我就是大名鼎鼎的“鲍伯出场  虫子死光光”的鲍伯邓肯
I am Bob Duncan of Bob's bugs be gone.
现在确实  没错  你可以购买莫雷大法
Now sure, yes, you can pay Murray.
然后把橘子汁喷的满屋子都是
To go and spray orange juice all over your house.
或者你可以主动出击
Or you can attack.
找到问题的根源
The problem at its source.
那么问题的根源在哪里呢
And what is that source?
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
我告诉你
I give you.
白蚁女王
The termite queen!
我会得到车  我会得到车
Gonna get a car. Gonna get a car.
白蚁女王
The termite queen,
是殖民王国的高贵的皇室妈妈
The grand royal mama of the colony,
她唯一的工作就是  不停的排卵
Her only job: Pumping out termite eggs.
昼夜不停
Around the clock.
看呐  白蚁卵来了
Behold termite eggs,
一天产3万颗
30,000 every single day.
去吧  孩子们  去吧
Go, my babies, go.
吃光木头  毁掉墙壁
Eat wood and destroy siding.
别慌  各位  别慌  安心坐着
Relax, everybody, relax. Keep your seats.
有办法了
There is a solution.
嘿  女王陛下
Here, your majesty,
尝尝邓肯大灌篮
Try the slam dunc.
啊
Ha!
我诅咒你  邓肯灌篮法
Curse you, slam dunc method.
我给萎了  你听到了吗  萎了
I'm rendered useless. Do you hear me? Useless.
唉  什么世道啊
Oh, what a world.
什么世道啊
What a world.
车
Car.
好的  你现在是要毁灭城市的巨婴
Okay, you're a 50-foot baby about to destroy the entire city.
开始
Action.
停
Cut!
你还想要我怎么样
What do you want me to do?
哥们  我们肯定
Dude, we're never gonna
拍不完这部戏  如果她总是跑掉的话
finish this movie if she keeps running off.
那我们怎么办  把她的鞋粘在地上
How do we solve that? Glue her shoes to the floor?
好的  这两个小不点再也逃不了了
Okay, these puppies aren't going anywhere.
查莉
Charlie.
哥们  你妈
Dude, your mom.
原来你在这儿  你们男孩子在干什么呢
There you are. What are you boys doing?
我们没有把鞋粘在地板上  真的没有
Not gluing shoes to the floor. That's for sure.
盖布里埃尔·邓肯
Gabriel Duncan!
她老是不听我们使唤
She wouldn't do what we wanted.
我早就应该知道了  每次你说你要照看查莉
I should have known. Every time you ask to watch Charlie,
-都是为了把她粘到某个地方  -妈
-It's because you wanna glue her to something. -Mom.
对不起了  男孩们  小小孩要离开梦工厂了
Sorry, boys, the kid's out of the picture.
妈  我们还没拍完戏呢
Mom, we're not done yet.
现在我们该做什么
Now what are we gonna do?
我们要拍怪物电影却没了怪物
We got a monster movie with no monster.
除非
Unless...
现在来点儿恐怖吧
Now rain down some terror.
欢迎致电咕唧炸鸡
Welcome to kwikki chikki.
你想尝试一下我们最新的蛋奶球吗
Would you like to try our new batter balls?
不想  很好
No. Good call.
我要一份咕唧炸鸡三号套餐
I will have the kwikki combo #3.
外加菜丝沙拉  卷曲薯条
With Cole slaw, Curly fries.
还有你明天得搬出去
And you have to move out by tomorrow.
P.J.  是你吗
P.J., is that you?
嗯  是我
Yeah, it's me.
我没法儿面对面跟你讲
I couldn't do this face to face,
所以我想只能对着鸡嘴说
So I thought I'd do it face to beak.
知道吗  肉汁  我把你当成哥哥一样爱你
Look, gravy, I love you like a brother,
但是你有点不注意个人卫生  而且快把我妈逼疯了
But you're kind of messy and you're driving my mom nuts,
所以你得走
And you gotta go.
诶对  我还要一份巧克力奶昔
Oh, and I'll have a chocolate milk shake.
说话呀  喂  别这样  你在吗
Talk to me, man, come on. You there?
嘿  你介意吗
Hey, do you mind?
我这儿有要事
I'm having a moment here.
肉汁  行了  兄弟  回答我呀
Gravy, come on. Dude, talk to me.
P.J.  我会找另一个地方去住的
P.J., I'll find another place to stay.
不要紧
It's no biggie.
诶对  你要的总共4块9毛5  放在了第二个窗口
Oh, and that'll be $4.95 at the second window.
对不起啊  兄弟
I'm sorry, man.
别在意
Don't worry about it.
你是我的兄弟嘛
You're my buddy.
事实上是你都不好意思向我开口
The fact that it was so hard for you to say this to me,
我是说  这意味深重
I mean, it means a lot.
那么我们没事了
So we good?
难道你想当没说吗
You wanna flap it out?
耶
Yeah.
老爸  我们进屋前
Dad, before we go in,
我有件事想跟你谈
there's something I wanted to talk to you about.
-什么事  甜心  -首先  你开心吗
-What's that, honey? -First, are you happy?
你开玩笑吧
Are you kidding me?
我欣喜欲狂了
I'm over the moon.
这是有史以来最棒的灭虫大会
That was the best bug convention ever.
那就好  那就好  因为我有个小请求
Great, great, 'cause there's something that I wanted to ask you.
其实  你知道吗  在你对我说之前
Actually, you know what? Before you do,
我想先跟你说
there's something I wanna say.
你知道吗  有时候我真的感觉
You know, sometimes I just feel.
你们这些孩子长得太快了  以至于
Like you kids are growing up so fast that...
你们都没有时间陪家里的老人了
That you just don't have time for your old man.
你知道吗
You know?
所以你说这个周末你要跟我一起去的时候
So when you asked to come with me this weekend,
甜心  你让我感觉特别幸福
Honey, you made me feel so great.
谢谢
Thank you.
我真的真的很爱你
And I love you very very much.
不好意思  你刚才问我什么来着
I'm sorry. What did you wanna ask me?
哦  我只是想说
Oh, I just wanted to say...
我也爱你  爸
I love you too, dad.
我也爱你
Love you too.
-嘿  -嘿  我的虫子怪回来了
-Hey. -Hey, there's my little bugaboos.
-会开得怎么样  -最成功的一次
-How was the convention? -The best ever.
嘿  泰迪  跟你老妈讲讲这事
Hey, Teddy, tell her all about it.
好的好的
Okeydokey.
他看起来特别高兴  你得到什么样的车了
He looks pretty happy. What kind of car you getting?
我做不到
I couldn't do it.
什么
What?
你让他乐翻了天却没得到任何好处
You got him all happied up for nothing?
看来你老妈要得到一双新鞋啰
Looks like mama's getting a new pair of shoes.
嗨  亲爱的鲍伯
Oh, Bob honey.
嗨  查莉
Hey, Charlie.
是的  我做了一件好事
Well, I did the right thing...
跟老爸参加灭虫大会去了
went with dad to the bug convention,
让他高兴得不得了
Made him real happy.
不幸的是  高兴得过了头
Unfortunately, so happy.
他邀请我明年再去
He invited me to go again next year.
我要演一支蚊子
I'm gonna be a mosquito.
-你在干什么  -测量你的翼展
-What are you doing? -Just measuring your wingspan.
-噢  -我们到时候要销售邓肯牌微波灭虫器
-Oh. -We're gonna be selling the Duncan zapper.
唉  微波灭蚊器
Oh, zapper!
听起来好痛苦
Sounds painful.
看来某天你也要参加各种灭虫大会了
Now someday you're gonna be going to these bug conventions.
真的  祝你好运  查莉
Yeah. Good luck, Charlie.
好的
Okay.
巨婴来袭  第一幕  第一场
Attack of the 50-foot baby, scene 1, take 1.
好的  你是个疯狂科学家  继续  行动
Okay, you're a mad scientist. Go on... Action!
现在我已经完成了我的超速成长配方
Now that I've finished my super growth formula,
该用来对普通的葡萄进行实验了
It's time to test it out on an ordinary grape.
奏效了
It works!
不  没有  那是个橡皮鸭
No it doesn't. It's a rubber ducky.
是啊  要是有人没把西瓜吃掉就好了
Well... If somebode hadn't eaten the watermelon,
我就不用临时发挥了
I wouldn't have to improvise.